Stan Lewis Collection of 45 rpm Records, 1965-1985 SC 48
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 1. 45rpm discs
  - Uniques; Stampley, Joe -- All These Things; You Know That I Love You, 1976; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    All These Things -- Producer: n/a; Composer: N. Neville; You Know That I Love You -- Producer: Rob Smith, Composer: J. Stampley
  - Violinaires -- Little Jesus Boy; White Christmas, 1973; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 81
    SL 2335-2336
    222
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/g45148hs3n
    Little Jesus Boy -- Producer: B. Patterson, Composer: Lewis; White Christmas -- Producer: Don Logan, Composer: Logan
  - White, Artie -- What Pleases You Pleases Me; Jimmie, 1984; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 82
    SL 3064-3063
    101
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s25x21ww8n
    What Pleases You Pleases Me -- Producer: Artie White, Composers: B. Jones, P. Richmond; Jimmie -- Producer: Artie White, Composer: A. White, S. Joseph
  - White, Artie -- Chain of Fools; Leanin' Tree, 1981; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 83
    SL 3190-3191
    111
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/791s45sn9f
    Chain of Fools -- Producer: Artie White, Composer: Gonald Covay; Leanin' Tree -- Producer: Artie White, Composer: B. Jones